

## **DHARANIKUMAR K**

**FULL STACK DEVELOPER** 



## CONTACT



**Phone** 

+91-9952638437



**Email** 

dharanfsd@gmail.com



**Address** 

Dusi, Kancheepuram, Tamilnadu



## **MY SKILLS**

- O HTML
- O CSS
- O BOOTSTRAP
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT JS
- NODEJS
- EXPRESS JS
- MONGODB



## **SOCIAL MEDIA**

PORTFOLIO

HTTPS://DHARANPORTFOLIO.NET LIFY.APP/

() LINKEDIN

HTTPS://WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/ DHARANIKUMARKFSD/

(>) GITHUB

HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/KDHARANI KUMAR



### **PROFILE INFO**

I'm a Mechanical Engineering & MBA Graduate. I have 5 years of experience in the Automobile Industries Quality Department. Now I have to change my career to the Software Industry. So I did the Complete Full Stack Developer (MERN) Course.

## Cana

#### **EDUCATION**

•	Diploma In Automobile Engineering Dusi Polytechnic College, Dusi	2009-2011
•	B.E - Mechanical Engineering  Arulmigu Meenakshi Amman College of Engineering AMACE  Vadamavandhal-Kancheepuram	2013-2016
<b>③</b>	MBA - Supply Chain Management University of Madras - Chennai	2018-2019
	OFFITIE A TION	

# CERTIFICATION

**Quality Trainee** 

$\odot$	Full Stack Development (MERN)	2022-2023
	Guvi - Chennai	

(3)

 $\odot$ 

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Web Design & Development

STARFLIT- Dusi, Kancheepuram

	Hyundai Mobis - Chennai	
•	<b>Quality Engineer</b> Rockman - Cheyyar	2016-2018
<b>③</b>	<b>Quality Engineer</b> TVS Sundaram Clayton - Chennai	2018-2019
<b>③</b>	Web Design & Development YoukoTech- Chennai	2020-2021

2011-2013

2021-Till Now